Guide to the Stanford University, School of Medicine, Department of Biochemistry, Bound Reprint Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Medicine, Department of Biochemistry, bound reprint collection
1961-1997
SC0955
Stanford University. School of Medicine. Dept. of Biochemistry.
8.5 Linear feet
This set of bound reprints of articles by faculty in the Department of Biochemistry was Arthur Kornberg’s set.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
This set of bound reprints of articles by faculty in the Department of Biochemistry was Arthur Kornberg’s set.
Access Terms
Kornberg, Arthur, 1918-2007; Stanford University. School of Medicine. Dept. of Biochemistry.
Collection Contents
- Reprints
  - 1961-1963 (Box 1)
  - 1964 (Box 1)
  - 1965 (Box 1)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - 1968 (Box 1)
  - 1969 (Box 1)
  - 1970 (Box 2)
  - 1971 (Box 2)
  - 1972 (Box 2)
  - 1973 (Box 2)
  - 1974 (Box 2)
  - 1975 (Box 2)
  - 1976 (Box 3)
  - 1977 (Box 3)
  - 1978 (Box 3)
  - 1979 (Box 3)
  - 1980 (Box 3)
  - 1981 (Box 3)
  - 1982 (Box 4)
  - 1983 (Box 4)
  - 1984 (Box 4)
  - 1985 (Box 4)
  - 1986 (Box 4)
  - 1987 (Box 4)
  - 1988 (Box 5)
  - 1989 (Box 5)
  - 1990 (Box 5)
  - 1991 (Box 5)
  - 1992 (Box 5)
  - 1993 (Box 5)
  - 1994 (Box 6)
  - 1995 (Box 6)
  - 1996 (Box 7)
  - 1997 (Box 7)